A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, Mexico, RG 6, SG 13 FA398
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Experimental Camp Files, 1943-1965; 2
  - General Files - Water Analysis, 1956-1957 (Box 72, Folder 814)